[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "prompt": "Mountain Dew was originally slang for:",
    "choices": [
      "Coffee",
      "Red Bull",
      "Whiskey",
      "Moonshine"
    ],
    "answer": "Moonshine"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "prompt": "JavaScript's creator spent this long creating it:",
    "choices": [
      "10 hours",
      "10 days",
      "10 weeks",
      "10 months"
    ],
    "answer": "10 days"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "prompt": "The Express route /api/:table/:id? does NOT match:",
    "choices": [
      "/api/users/",
      "/api/table/id/1",
      "/api/table/2"
    ],
    "answer": "/api/table/id/1"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "prompt": "In a database with Parent/Child records, the record with the primary key is pointed to by the record with the foreign key.",
    "choices": [
      "true",
      "false"
    ],
    "answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "prompt": "All of these are examples of ORMs except:",
    "choices": [
      "Express",
      "Sequelize",
      "A custom library taking callbacks",
      "Mongoose"
    ],
    "answer": "Express"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "prompt": "A package.json gains a dependency via:",
    "choices": [
      "npm init -y",
      "npm install express",
      "npm install -S express",
      "npm blame"
    ],
    "answer": "npm install -S express"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "prompt": "Which of these REST actions is *mismatched* to its CRUD verb?",
    "choices": [
      "CREATE - INSERT",
      "GET - SELECT",
      "PATCH - UPDATE",
      "DESTROY - DELETE"
    ],
    "answer": "CREATE - INSERT"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "prompt": "All of these are reasons to render HTML on the server with Handlebars EXCEPT",
    "choices": [
      "Search Engines (Google)",
      "Requires higher-powered device to render the page",
      "Faster initial load of content",
      "Requires lower-powered device to render the page"
    ],
    "answer": "Requires higher-powered device to render the page"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "prompt": "Handlebars triple-mustache will allow HTML from your database into the page as-is.",
    "choices": [
      "Yay! Just what I need!",
      "Yay! (Better look out for malicious user content)",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "Yay! (Better look out for malicious user content)"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "prompt": "Heroku will configure your app's database string via:",
    "choices": [
      "process.argv[2]",
      "process.env.PORT",
      "process.argv.JAWSDB_URL",
      "process.env.JAWSDB_URL"
    ],
    "answer": "process.env.JAWSDB_URL"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "prompt": "Whether you think you can, or you can't - you're correct.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  }
]